promocodesforyou.com 2013-12-04

# Privacy | PromoCodesForYou

**Are you wondering what kinds of information we might collect from you?**

Well, the truth is that we don't collect much. We collect your email when you subscribe to our newsletter. That's about it.

**What do we use your email for?**

You signed up for our newsletter so you probably know that we're using it to send you emails. This email you provided may be used to send you deals, information, or updates about our site and services.

**How do we protect your information, you might ask?**

We take several security measures to make sure your information is safe. And we don't sell your emails, if that's what you're thinking. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we do. If you're wondering what a nice desert has to do with anything, in the world of the internet, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider uses to recognize your browser and remember certain information. This is actually how we get paid -- the cookie tells the merchant that we sent them a consumer that made a purchase.

At some point, we might use cookies to save your preferences for future visits to our site or to gather data about our site traffic. If we did this, it would be to try to improve your experience on our site. 

**Do we disclose any information that you provide to outside parties?**

Nope. We don't trade, sell, or transfer any of your personal information to any outside parties. There might be times when we share your information with trusted third parties (people who help us to operate or develop our website) but we only do this when those third parties have agreed to keep your information confidential. We would also release your information if we believed that it was necessary to comply with the law or protect our safety, property, or rights or the safety, property, or rights of others. Having said all that, we may very well provide non-personally identifiable visitor information to others for advertising, marketing, or other uses .

**Third party links**

At our discretion, we might, on occasion, promote third party products (or services) on our website. Keep in mind that these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, that might be different from our own. We therefore cannot be held accountable for the content and activities of any sites that we link to or promote. Having said that, if there is ever anything on a site that we link to or promote that causes concern, we would appreciate being notified.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We greatly value your privacy so we have taken the necessary precautions in order to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Thus, we will not distribute your personal information to any outside parties without first getting your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not collect any information from those who are under the age of thirteen. Our website, content and services are all geared towards people who are at least 13 years old.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 6-25-13 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may visit our [Contact ](http://www.promocodesforyou.com/index.php?page=contact_us) page or use the information below: 

Linfield Media  
2121 Cloverfield Blvd., Suite 132  
Santa Monica, CA 90404
